longhaircareforum.com 2018-08-24

# Privacy Policy | Long Hair Care Forum

This privacy policy sets out how Long Hair Care Forum uses and protects any information that you provide, while using Long Hair Care Forum products and services. This includes, but is not limited to, LongHairCareForum.com and any associated websites and sub-domains.

Long Hair Care Forum is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Any information provided by you to Long Hair Care Forum, by which you can be identified, will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.

Long Hair Care Forum may change this policy as and when necessary. It is your responsibility to check this privacy policy periodically to ensure you agree with any changes.

## What information we collect

When using any products and services provided by Long Hair Care Forum, we require some all of the following information:

  * username
  * date of birth
  * email address

Additionally, while using the LongHairCareForum.com website, any associated websites and sub-domains, some or all of the following information may be collected:

  * Internet Protocol (IP) address
  * geographical location
  * browser type and version
  * operating system
  * referral source
  * length of visit, page views, website navigation and any other related browsing activity

## What we do with the information we collect

The information you provide to Long Hair Care Forum is required for, but not limited to, the following reasons:

  * internal record keeping
  * access to the LongHairCareForum.com website, associated websites and sub-domains
  * account management
  * account reset
  * confirmation of email address from the user
  * sending notices of subscribed content

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to Long Hair Care Forum is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect.

## How we use cookies and IP addresses

LongHairCareForum.com, any associated websites and sub-domains, use small text files, called cookies, to store information in your web browser. The information stored may include preferences, session identification, HTTP information, and IP address.

You can set your browser to not receive cookies, but this may limit your ability to use LongHairCareForum.com and any associated websites and sub-domains.

IP addresses of computers used to visit LongHairCareForum.com and any associated websites and sub-domains are stored in our database. This includes when first registering for an account, managing your account details, writing a private or public message or performing any other transaction which results in data being transferred to or from your computer and the website in question.

Your IP address is not visible to the public at any time.

## Links to other websites

LongHairCareForum.com, any associated websites and sub-domains, may contain links to other websites. These websites may or may not be affiliated with Long Hair Care Forum.

Long Hair Care Forum has no control over any external websites therefore clicking any link which results in you visiting an external website will result in this privacy policy no longer applying and Long Hair Care Forum cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites.

## Controlling your personal information

When using the LongHairCareForum.com forum, you may choose to limit public viewing of applicable personal information through the settings located in the Privacy section of your account.

Long Hair Care Forum will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your explicit permission or are required by law to do so. 

If you discover any of the information Long Hair Care Forum holds for you is incorrect or incomplete, that you are unable to change yourself, please contact us as soon as possible so the necessary changes can be made.

Published:
    Apr 15, 2015
Page Views:
    14,644
